https://www.elephants.com/cookie-policy

ES-logo
Providing herd, home, rest, refuge, and individualized care for life, and raising public awareness of the complex needs and challenges of elephants.
Cookie Policy
Effective Date: April 21, 2020The site https://www.elephants.com/ (“Site”) is owned and operated by The Elephant Sanctuary in Tennessee (“The Elephant Sanctuary,” “we,” “us,” or “our”). This Website Cookie Policy is intended to tell users (“user(s),” “you,” or “your”) about our Site’s collection, use, and dissemination practices regarding information that users provide to us through our Site or the services offered therein (collectively, the “Services”). This Website Cookie Policy is incorporated into the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use by reference. 1.	Cookies, Anonymous Identifiers, Web Beacons, and Other Internet Tracking TechnologyWe utilize Cookies, Anonymous Identifiers, Web Beacons, and other Internet tracking technology to collect information from a user’s computer, mobile, or other device. A “Cookie” is a data file that is created and stored on your computer’s hard drive when you visit our Services.
An “Anonymous Identifier” is a random string of characters that is used for similar reasons as Cookies. We use Cookies and Anonymous Identifiers to become more familiar with users through the study of analytics. Some portions of the Services require the use of Cookies for proper function.
Anonymous Identifiers can be used where Cookie technology is not available.
You may refuse to accept Cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your web browser.
If you select this setting, you may be unable to access certain parts of our Services.
Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse Cookies, we will issue Cookies when you direct your browser to our Services. A “Web Beacon” is an object embedded into a web page or an e-mail that collects various data. A Web Beacon is known by several common terms, such as a web bug, tag, page tag, tracking bug, tracking pixel, pixel tag, web pixel, targeting pixel, re-targeting pixel, and clear gif.
Web Beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier that may be included on our Services for several purposes, including to deliver or communicate with Cookies, to track and measure the performance of our Services, and to monitor how many visitors view our Services. Unlike Cookies, which are stored on the device, Web Beacons are typically embedded invisibly on web pages or in e-mails.
When used within e-mail, for example, a web beacon can track whether a user opens a message, clicks on a link within the e-mail, and similar actions.
We also use other, similar Internet tracking technology to monitor a user’s actions coming to our Services, moving through our Services, and after leaving our Services.2.	How We Use CookiesWe use Cookies to track how our users access and use our Services, to learn when and how users visit the Services, to make personalized features and other services available to users, to learn which terms are used, to learn which websites direct users to our Services, to compile and analyze aggregate statistics and trends, and to otherwise help administer and improve the Services.
We also use Cookies to help display certain information on the Services and to improve your enjoyment and convenience when using or visiting our Services; for example, by remembering your contact and other information when you access or use the Services. We also use Cookies to facilitate login and access actions to enter a user account.
For more information on how we use the information we gather from our users’ activity on the Services, please see our Privacy Policy.Specifically, we use strictly necessary Cookies, which allow users to access and use our Services, and which allow us to deliver our Services to users.
For example, when a user uses our Services and logs in to his or her user account, we use Session ID Cookies and JavaScript to check Cookies.
We use performance Cookies that allow us to track usage.
This allows us to learn more about how users use the Services so that we make changes and improvements, as necessary.We use targeting Cookies that measure the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns and to track sites users have visited so that we can measure the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns and so that we can use donations efficiently.Please be aware that this Website Cookie Policy does not govern the use of third-party websites or services or providers of third-party services.3.	Change Settings From Within Your BrowserOur Cookie acceptance form makes it easy for you to enable and disable all non-essential Cookies, however, it may not prevent all Cookies from other websites being sent to your computer, mobile, or other device.
To do this you may change your settings from within your browser by going to the “help” function on most browsers.
If you choose to have your browser refuse Cookies, then it is likely that some areas of the Services will not function properly when you use them.The instructions for these vary from browser to browser and they may change from time to time as new versions are released. Here are some links to instructions for the most common browsers:Microsoft Internet ExplorerClick here for Microsoft Internet ExplorerMozilla FirefoxClick here for Mozilla FirefoxGoogle ChromeClick here for Google ChromeSafariClick here for SafariFor other browsers, try searching for “managing Cookies in [browser name].”If you have any questions or concerns about our use of Cookies and other tracking technologies, please send us an e-mail at privacy@elephants.com.
To learn more about our Privacy Policy, please read the policy here.4.	List of cookies we use on our website:Facebook_fbc, _fbpGoogle Analytics_ga, _gid, __utma, __utmzHotjar_hjid, _hjIncludedInSample, _hjMinimizedPollsLaravellaravel_session, XSRF_TOKENGiveCloudGivecloud_sessionIntercomintercom-session-cs01jxl6We collect non-personal information through our Internet log files, which record data such as browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our Services and products. This information may be used to analyze trends, to administer our Services and products, to monitor the use of our products and services, and to gather general demographic information. We may link this information to personal information for these and other purposes such as personalizing a user’s experience on our Services and evaluating our Services and products in general.
+
Current Residents
Learn More
Donate
Sign up for EleNews!
We use cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website. Learn more
I agree
